<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
        Changelog Version Color Coding Rules:
        1. Dev / Nightly : Crimson #DC143C    (Experimental builds, potentially unstable)
        2. Alpha         : Orange     (Early testing phase, features may be incomplete)
        3. Beta          : DodgerBlue (More stable testing phase, nearing feature completion)
        4. RC            : Purple     (Release Candidate, polish and bug fixing phase)
        5. Release       : Green      (Stable public release)
    -->

<resources>
    <!--Changelog-->
    <string-array name="changelog" translatable="false">
        <item>@string/changelog_1_6_2_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_1_6_1_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_1_6_0_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_1_5_10_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_158_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_156_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_155_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_154_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_153_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_152_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_151_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_150_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_141_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_140_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_132_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_131_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_124_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_123_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_122_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_121_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_110_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_104_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_103_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_102_beta</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_101_beta</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Points to the changelog of current version.-->
    <string name="release_notes" translatable="false">@string/changelog_1_6_3_beta</string>

    <!--1.6.3-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_1_6_3_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.6.3)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Community Edition:</b> Introduced a new build flavor tailored for open-source environments, replacing Play Store links with GitHub "Stars" and removing proprietary billing components.
        \n✓ <b>Abstracted Market Interactions:</b> Implemented a new App Market Manager to handle updates and reviews across different platforms (Play Store vs. GitHub).
        \n✓ <b>Multi-Flavor Billing Support:</b> Refactored the billing system into "Actual" (Google Play) and "Stub" (Premium/Gold) implementations to support restricted regions and special editions.
        \n✓ <b>Analytics Abstraction:</b> Telemetry is now flavor-aware; standard builds use Firebase/Crashlytics, while Community and Gold versions use a privacy-focused no-op implementation.
        \n✓ <b>Security &amp; Stability:</b>
        \n    • Added RSA signature verification for in-app purchases.
        \n    • Improved update flow error handling to prevent crashes in non-Google Play environments.
        \n✓ <b>Under the Hood:</b>
        \n    • Upgraded build infrastructure: <b>Gradle 9.5.0</b>, <b>AGP 9.3.0</b>, and <b>Kotlin 2.4.10</b>.
        \n    • Updated project metadata and branding from "Audiofy" to "OnePlayer".
    </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.6.2-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_1_6_2_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.6.2-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Multi-Flavor Support:</b> Introduced specialized editions: Standard, Community, Plus, and Gold.
        \n✓ <b>Video Scaling Persistence:</b> Fixed an issue where video scale settings were lost when switching between video and audio content.
        \n✓ <b>UI Refinements:</b> Improved Labs Mode visual alignment and refined storage permission dialogs with justified text for better readability.
        \n✓ <b>Under the Hood:</b>
        \n    • Migrated to a centralized `AppConfig` system for better metadata handling.
        \n    • Expanded Firebase support for Full and Pro variants.
        \n    • Upgraded to <b>Android 37</b> (compileSdk).
    </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.6.1-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_1_6_1_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.6.1-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Enhanced Promotions:</b> Introduced a smarter rotation system for promotional messages and tips.
        \n✓ <b>IAP Integration:</b> New dynamic prompts for In-App Purchases, featuring high-priority products with clear calls-to-action.
        \n✓ <b>Frequency Adjustment:</b> Increased the frequency of helpful prompts and "What\'s New" notifications for a better discovery experience.
        \n✓ <b>Modernized Foundation:</b>
        \n    • Upgraded target SDK to <b>Android 37</b>.
        \n    • Updated core dependencies including Kotlin 2.4.0 and AGP 9.2.1.
        \n    • Refreshed Media3 (1.10.1), Coil (3.5.0), and Play Billing (9.0.0).
        \n✓ <b>UX Improvements:</b>
        \n    • Isolated "What\'s New" logic to trigger independently with a smoother delay.
        \n    • Standardized snackbar durations and added specific iconography for purchase prompts.
    </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.6.0-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_1_6_0_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.6.0-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Background Playback Policies:</b> Introduced a new system to control media behavior when the app is hidden. Choose between "None" (pause), "Audio Only" (stops video but keeps audio), or "All" (keep playing).
        \n✓ <b>App Visibility Tracking:</b> The playback service now accurately tracks when the app is in the foreground or background to enforce playback rules.
        \n✓ <b>Settings Update:</b> Added a "Background Play Mode" selector in the settings screen.
        \n✓ <b>Smart Enforcement:</b> Automatically pauses video playback when entering the background if the current policy doesn\'t allow it.
        \n✓ <b>New Icon:</b> Added a new "Exit to App" icon for the background playback setting.
        \n✓ <b>Under the Hood:</b>
        \n    • Renamed the internal `relay` system to `remote` for better architectural clarity.
        \n    • Improved MIME type detection to distinguish between audio and video content more reliably.
        \n    • Updated key dependencies (nav3, androidx-koin) and bumped version to 1.6.0.
    </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.5.10-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_1_5_10_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.10-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ Enhanced subtitle rendering with native Media3 support for richer, more accurate captions
        \n✓ Upgraded playback engine (Media3 v1.10.0) for improved stability and performance
        \n✓ Cleaner UI integration with new SubtitleView in Compose
        \n✓ Dependency updates and minor fixes for smoother playback experience
    </font>
    </string>


    <!--1.5.8-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_158_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.8-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Labs Mode:</b> A new experimental features hub. First experiment: Long-Press to Seek on the Now Playing screen.
        \n✓ <b>Playback UX:</b> Clicking a video now jumps directly to Now Playing after starting playback.
        \n✓ <b>Icon System Refactor:</b> Replaced `material-icons-extended` with local XML vector drawables for better performance and simpler icon management.
        \n✓ <b>Build &amp; Dependency Updates:</b>
        \n    • Upgraded Gradle (9.1.0 → 9.3.1) and refreshed key dependencies (AGP, Kotlin, Media3, Compose BOM, Navigation, etc.).
    </font>
</string>


    <!--1.5.6-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_156_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.6-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ <b>Icon System Refactor:</b> Replaced the `material-icons-extended` library with local XML vector drawables, improving performance by avoiding reflection and streamlining icon management.
        \n✓ <b>Build &amp; Dependency Cleanup:</b>
        \n    • Removed the unused `telemetry` feature module.
        \n    • Refactored and organized the version catalog (`libs.versions.toml`) for better clarity and maintenance.
        \n✓ <b>Code Modernization:</b>
        \n    • Implemented a type-safe `Res` object for resource access (e.g., `Res.string.delete`), enhancing code readability and safety.
        \n    • Centralized and renamed theme-related enums (`NightMode`, `AccentColorPolicy`) for better organization.
    </font></string>


    <!--1.5.5-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_155_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.5-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ Modernized UI handling:
        \n   • Adopted WindowCompat.enableEdgeToEdge(window) for improved system bar &amp; cutout support.
        \n✓ Deprecated API cleanup:
        \n   • Replaced setDecorFitsSystemWindows(window, false) with enableEdgeToEdge(window).
    </font></string>


    <!--1.5.4-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_154_beta" translatable="false">
    <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.4-beta)\n</font></b>
    <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ Updated dependencies for improved stability:
        \n   • media3 → 1.9.0
        \n   • androidx-activity-compose → 1.12.2
        \n   • google-billing-ktx → 8.3.0
        \n✓ Enabled Compose compiler stability configuration.
        \n✓ Refined two-pane layout logic:
        \n   • Aspect ratio-based triggers for better tablet portrait handling.
        \n   • Horizontal split ratio set to 0.55f.
        \n   • Added 10dp spacing between panes.
        \n✓ Library view now adapts to aspect ratio for consistent single-pane in portrait.
        \n✓ Acrylic effect fine-tuned with adjusted luminance and alpha for subtle theme improvements.
    </font></string>


    <!--1.5.3-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_153_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.3-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ Refreshed icons across app, splash, and TV for a cleaner look.
            \n✓ Added intermediate progress indicator to improve feedback during delayed startup.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.5.2-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_152_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.2-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ Resolved issue causing incomplete splash animation.
        \n✓ Added monochromatic icon for themed app icon support.
        \n✓ Introduced TV channel and banner icons.
        \n✓ Implemented a robust Analytics module in core (migrated from telemetry).
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.5.1-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_151_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.1-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ Splash animation delay increased to 1000ms for smoother transitions.
            \n✓ Fixed issue where sharedBounds background was not cleared in Console when disabled.
            \n✓ Introduced a concrete Analytics implementation in the core module (moved from telemetry).
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.5.0-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_150_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.5.0-beta)\n</font></b>
       <font color='grey'>
        \n✓ Improved immersive experience by removing background from system navigation.
        \n✓ Added a toggle to wait for the splash animation to finish before continuing into the app.
        \n✓ Added a toggle to enable shared element transitions between the in-app widget and the Now Playing screen.
        \n✓ <b>Gestures:</b>
             - Added background styling around gesture visual feedback.
             - Implemented safe area checks to prevent gestures outside a 30dp boundary.
             - Fixed issue where double-tap seek incorrectly registered a value of 2 on the first multi-tap instead of 1.
             - Fixed brightness control to start from at least 10% when automatic mode is enabled.
             - Added logic to intercept hardware Enter keys (useful for TVs and similar devices).
             - Fixed issue causing repeated toast messages when holding click for long press.
             - Fixed issue where the in-app widget appeared when tapping “Show Equalizer” in Console.
        \n✓ <b>TimeBar:</b> Fixed issue with enable/disable logic not working correctly.
    </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.4.1-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_141_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.4.1-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Animated Splash Screen:</b> Introducing a new animated splash screen for Android 12+ for a more dynamic startup experience.
            \n✓ <b>Smarter Video Playback:</b>
            \n    - The screen now stays on only when video is playing and turns off when paused to save battery.
            \n    - Subtitle display logic has been improved to prevent cues from disappearing abruptly.
            \n    - The layout of the seek bar in a locked video player has been refined for better alignment.
            \n✓ <b>UI &amp; Icon Updates:</b>
            \n    - Updated several icons, including a new horizontal "more" icon in the player console.
            \n    - The seek bar is now disabled when the player is idle.
            \n    - Reduced the default font size for subtitles for better visual balance.
            \n✓ <b>Code Refinements:</b>
            \n    - Restructured player gesture handling for improved readability and maintainability.
            \n    - Introduced new UI components like `FloatRange` and `LottieAnimatedIcon` to streamline the codebase.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.4.0-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_140_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.4.0-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Advanced Gesture Controls:</b> The player now features a completely rewritten gesture system for a more intuitive experience.
            \n    - <b>Multi-Tap to Seek:</b> Quickly tap multiple times on the sides of the screen to seek forward or backward.
            \n    - <b>Long-Press for Speed:</b> Press and hold anywhere on the screen to temporarily double the playback speed.
            \n    - <b>Precise Drag Controls:</b> Drag vertically on the left/right side of the screen to adjust brightness/volume, or drag horizontally to scrub through the timeline.
            \n✓ <b>Enhanced Player UI:</b>
            \n    - Redesigned console with new background and play button styles for better customization.
            \n    - Improved visibility logic ensures controls hide and show more smoothly, especially in locked mode.
            \n✓ <b>Smarter Playback Restoration:</b>
            \n    - The player now correctly restores its last playback position and shuffle order on startup.
            \n    - Fixed an issue where content duration was lost after an app restart, preventing an infinite progress bar.
            \n✓ <b>Performance &amp; Code Quality:</b>
            \n    - Major refactoring of the player console and gesture handling for improved maintainability and clarity.
            \n    - Enabled the optimized R8 resource shrinker to reduce app size.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.3.2-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_132_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.3.2-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Performance Boost:</b> Enhanced Jetpack Compose performance and stability by enabling strong skipping and marking key UI components as stable. This helps reduce unnecessary UI updates and provides a smoother experience.
            \n✓ <b>UI Layout Refinements:</b> Adjusted layout breakpoints for better display on various screen sizes.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.3.1-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_131_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.3.1-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Video Thumbnail Support:</b> The player now displays thumbnails for video files, making it easier to identify your media at a glance.
            \n✓ <b>Enhanced Media Notifications:</b> Album art and video thumbnails now load more efficiently in Media3 notifications, thanks to integration with the Coil image loading library.
            \n✓ <b>UI Refinements:</b> The player console has been updated with a subtler gradient and simplified layout constraints for a cleaner look.
            \n✓ <b>New Icon:</b> Added a new stop icon for future use.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.2.4-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_124_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.2.4-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Evenly Spaced Layouts:</b> Introduced a new `spacing` parameter to horizontal chains, simplifying the creation of evenly spaced UI elements. This has been applied to the options row in the player console.
            \n✓ <b>Dependency Updates:</b>
            \n    - Updated Jetpack Compose to `1.10.0-rc01`.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.2.3-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_123_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.2.3-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Finer Playback Speed Control:</b>
            \n    - The playback speed range has been expanded to <b>0.25x – 8.0x</b> (previously 3.0x).
            \n    - Enjoy more precise adjustments with a smaller step interval of <b>0.05x</b>.
            \n✓ <b>Improved Widget Configuration:</b>
            \n    - The layout of the bottom bar has been rearranged for better usability.
            \n    - Added a fallback text of "N/A" for purchase buttons when the price isn\'t available.
            \n✓ <b>Internal Refactoring:</b> Replaced a custom UI scaling modifier with the standard Jetpack Compose implementation, simplifying the codebase and improving performance.
          </font>
    </string>


    <!--1.2.2-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_122_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.2.2-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Streamlined Widget Configuration:</b> The widget setup screen has been simplified. We\'ve replaced the horizontal swipe gesture with easy-to-use left/right arrow buttons for a more straightforward navigation experience.
            \n✓ <b>Performance &amp; UI Polish:</b>
            \n    - Optimized the scaling modifier used across the app, leading to better performance and smoother animations.
            \n    - Standardized the layout, padding, and icon sizes across all home screen widgets for a more consistent and polished look.
            \n    - Updated the app name from "OnePlayer" to "One Player" (with a space) in a few places for brand consistency.
        </font>
    </string>

    <string name="changelog_121_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.2.1-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>All-New TimeBar:</b> The progress bar has been completely redesigned from the ground up for a smoother, more interactive experience.
            \n    - <b>Enhanced Animations:</b> Enjoy slick animations when you interact with the time bar.
            \n    - <b>Buffering Indicator:</b> A new loading animation shows you exactly when the media is buffering.
            \n    - <b>Keyboard Accessible:</b> Fully navigable with keyboard controls for seeking.
            \n✓ <b>Faster Playback Startup:</b> Media now prepares for playback as soon as you open the player, reducing the delay before you can press play.
            \n✓ <b>Cleaner "Recently Played" List:</b> The "Recently Played" section no longer shows duplicate tracks.
            \n✓ <b>UI &amp; Bug Fixes:</b> Made several layout adjustments in the player for better organization and fixed minor bugs.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.1.0-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_110_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.1.0-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Subtitle Support:</b> You can now watch videos with subtitles! Select a subtitle track from the new unified track selection menu.
            \n✓ <b>Unified Track Selection:</b> The audio, video, and subtitle track selection dialogs have been merged into one. Easily switch between track types and make your selection in a single, streamlined interface.
            \n✓ <b>Faster Remote Media Loading:</b> Adding media from URLs (HTTP/HTTPS) is now significantly faster. We now fetch metadata without downloading the entire file first, reducing delays.
            \n✓ <b>UI Refinements:</b>
            \n    - Adjusted the range for the "Grid Item Size" slider for better control.
            \n    - The track selection list no longer shows duplicate track names.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.0.4-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_104_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.0.4-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ Fixed a crash caused by duplicate keys in the library\'s recents section.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.0.3-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_103_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.0.3-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>Enhanced Error Handling:</b> Added detailed snackbar notifications for failed dynamic feature installations, including an option to view specific error codes.
            \n✓ <b>In-App Purchase Fix:</b> Corrected the identifier for the "Remove Ads" in-app purchase to ensure it functions as intended.
            \n✓ <b>UI Refinements:</b>
            \n    - Adjusted the BottomAppBar\'s padding to prevent it from overlapping with system navigation gestures.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.0.2-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_102_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.0.2-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b>New Look &amp; Feel:</b> Refreshed the app with new launcher icons and a redesigned splash screen for a modern identity.
            \n
            \n✓ <b>Player Enhancements:</b>
            \n    - Fixed the double-tap to seek gesture to correctly skip 10 seconds per tap.
            \n    - Easily show system bars in fullscreen by swiping from the screen edge.
            \n    - Improved the control layout in the landscape player for a cleaner look.
            \n    - The privacy policy link in settings now works correctly.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--1.0.0-beta-->
    <string name="changelog_101_beta" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.0.1-beta)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b><u>Rebranded from "Audiofy" to "OnePlayer"</u></b>
            \n    - This includes a new application ID, updated package names, and a fresh user-facing name.
            \n✓ <b><u>Minimum SDK Increased:</u></b>
            \n    - The minimum required Android version has been raised from Android 6.0 (API 23) to Android 9.0 (API 28) to leverage modern Android features and ensure a more stable experience.
            \n✓ <b><u>Dependency Updates:</u></b>
            \n    - Updated essential libraries like Kotlin and Compose to their latest versions for improved performance and stability.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v1.0.0-test01-->
    <string name="changelog_400_test01" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='purple'>(v1.0.0-beta01)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n✓ <b><u>Six New Player Widget Styles:</u></b>
            \n    - <b>Tiramisu:</b> Inspired by the Android 13 media notification, with a full-width album art background and centered controls.
            \n    - <b>GradientGroves:</b> Features a vibrant gradient and a unique "double vision" artwork effect.
            \n    - <b>RedVioletCake:</b> Based on the Android 11 media notification, with large artwork on the right and controls on the left.
            \n    - <b>DiskDynamo:</b> Showcases a rotating CD-style album art that animates while playing.
            \n    - <b>MistyDream:</b> A glassmorphism-style widget with a blurred background and a large, stylized chronometer.
            \n    - <b>SkewedDynamic:</b> A dynamic design with slanted shapes for both the widget body and album art.
            \n
            \n✓ <b><u>Refined Gesture Control:</u></b>
            \n    - The delay for the double-tap to seek gesture has been significantly reduced from 1000ms to 200ms, making it feel much more responsive.
        </font>
    </string>
</resources>